(this.webpackJsonpquiz=this.webpackJsonpquiz||[]).push([[0],{20:function(e,t,s){},36:function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t);var r=s(2),n=s(0),i=s.n(n),a=s(10),c=s.n(a),o=(s(20),s.p+"static/media/undraw_skateboard_d6or.bcd4f55a.svg"),l=s.p+"static/media/undraw_programmer_imem.828147b9.svg";var d=function(){return Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"img",children:[Object(r.jsx)("img",{className:"pic",src:o,alt:"Olympics"}),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"block"},children:[Object(r.jsx)("h1",{children:Object(r.jsx)("u",{children:"We're Up to Snow Good"})}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)("h3",{className:"typewriter",children:Object(r.jsx)("b",{children:"Quiz me Up!- A fun Quiz app :)"})})]}),Object(r.jsx)("img",{className:"pic",src:l,alt:"Programmer"})]})},j=s(18),x=s(55),h=s.p+"static/media/Person.929310ff.svg",b=s(52),u=s(53),m=s(54),w=s.p+"static/media/Celebration.a1537b21.svg",O=s.p+"static/media/Lost.991dfe20.svg",p=s.p+"static/media/undraw_Winter_olympics_p07j (1).7bc07d16.svg";function g(){var e=[{questionText:"When was the first Winter Olympics?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"1945",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1896",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1924",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"1936",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How many events are there in the Winter Olympics?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"105",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"102",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"100",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"104",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which is the only country to have won at least one gold medal in every Winter Olympics?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"USA",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Russia",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Norway",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Britain",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"No country in the southern hemisphere has ever even applied to host the Winter Olympics.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Where were the first modern Olympic Winter Games held?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Stockholm, Sweden",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chamonix, France",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Salt Lake, UT",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Moscow, Russia",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The VIII Olympic Winter Games saw the inclusion of which new women's competition?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Figure Skating",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Ski-jumping",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Speed Skating",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Bobsled",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What is the only indoor Winter Olympics sport that does not involve ice skates?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Skiing",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Snowboarding",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Luge",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Curling",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"In addition to Biathlon, what is the only other Winter Olympic sport in which the United States never won a gold medal?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Ice Hockey",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Figure Skating",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cross-country skiing",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Nordic Combined",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Who is the oldest person to receive a Winter Olympics medal?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Anders Haugen",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Sonja Henie",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Jeff Pain",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Avery Brundage",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What are the only two countries south of the equator to win medals at the Winter Olympics Games?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Australia and New Zealand",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"New Zealand and South Africa",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"South Africa and Argentina",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Australia and Argentina",isCorrect:!1}]}],t=Object(n.useState)(0),s=Object(j.a)(t,2),i=s[0],a=s[1],c=Object(n.useState)(!1),o=Object(j.a)(c,2),l=o[0],d=o[1],g=Object(n.useState)(0),T=Object(j.a)(g,2),C=T[0],y=T[1];return Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"app",children:[Object(r.jsx)("img",{src:h,alt:"Person",className:"person"}),l?C>e.length/2?Object(r.jsx)(x.a,{className:"quizCard",style:{backgroundImage:"radial-gradient(rgb(255,255,255), #2ecc71)"},children:Object(r.jsxs)(b.a,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{children:["You scored ",C," out of ",e.length,"!"]}),Object(r.jsx)("img",{className:"celeb",src:w,alt:"Celebration"})]})]})}):Object(r.jsx)(x.a,{className:"quizCard",style:{backgroundImage:"radial-gradient(rgb(255,255,255), #e74c3c)"},children:Object(r.jsxs)(b.a,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{children:["You scored ",C," out of ",e.length," :("]}),Object(r.jsx)("img",{className:"celeb",src:O,alt:"Better Luck Next time"})]})]})}):Object(r.jsx)(r.Fragment,{children:Object(r.jsxs)(x.a,{className:"quizCard",style:{backgroundImage:"radial-gradient(rgb(255,255,255), #FFC312)"},children:[Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"question-count",children:Object(r.jsx)(u.a,{children:Object(r.jsx)("span",{children:Object(r.jsxs)("i",{children:["Question ",i+1,"/",e.length]})})})}),Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:Object(r.jsx)("b",{children:e[i].questionText})}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{})]}),Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[i].answerOptions.map((function(t){return Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"option",children:[Object(r.jsx)(m.a,{variant:"contained",color:"primary",onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&y(C+1);var s=i+1;s<e.length?a(s):d(!0)}(t.isCorrect)},children:t.answerText}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{})]})}))})]})}),Object(r.jsx)("img",{src:p,alt:"olympics",className:"olympics"})]})}var T=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&s.e(3).then(s.bind(null,56)).then((function(t){var s=t.getCLS,r=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,i=t.getLCP,a=t.getTTFB;s(e),r(e),n(e),i(e),a(e)}))};c.a.render(Object(r.jsxs)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(d,{}),Object(r.jsx)(g,{})]}),document.getElementById("root")),T()}},[[36,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2c2afe6a.chunk.js.map